

+353 (0) 873327791

catsalazar311@gmail.com

**in** /Catherine-Salvargh

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Certificate in Fund Accounting**

**Dublin Business School** NAV calculation, investment compliance, UCITS and AIFM Fund regulations

2018-2019

#### Honorous Bachelor degree of Arts

The University of Valencia, Spain 2012 - 2016

#### **SKILLS**

Excel

CRM-Salesforce

**Fund Operations** 

Transfer Agency

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

### LANGUAGES

- English Cambridge CAE (C1)
- Spanish Native

# CATHERINE SALAZAR

Operations / Client Service Manager

## **ABOUT ME**

Dynamic, high performing, professional with 8+ years of experience in Financial Services, Investment Operations, Fund Administration Institutional client services and client onboaring.

My educational background in humanities has helped me develop great communication skills and the critical skills to help enhance processes and procedures.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Guggenheim Partners IM** 2019 - 2024

Operations and Client Service

Senior Associate / Manager

Jan 2023 - Aug 2024

- EU Institutional Client Service
- Client Reporting Analisys
- Outsourcing oversight
- Team manager
- Reported to the Head of CS

**Onboarding Associate** 

Oct 2021 - Jan 2023

**Analyst** 

Jun 2019 - Oct 2021

#### State Street Bank

2016 - 2019

Investor, Distributor Services

Senior Associate

Aug 2018 - Jun 2019

- Mutual and Hedge Funds Transfer Agency
- Supervision of the associate's workload

Associate II

Jan 2018 – Jul 2018

**Associate** 

Jan 2017 – Jan 2018

#### REFERENCES

Guggenheim Partners:

Suzanne Stone

Head of CS

#### Rajani Clyne

Julio Quintero

+1 (917) 327 1762

Chief Compliance Officer +44 (0) 7966 933261

Head of EU Legal +44 (0) 7825 589393